Guide to the Regents Hill Halls Photographs 2000-2006
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Regents Hill Halls Photographs
2000-2006
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
PC 179
0.25 Linear feet of shelf space 1 box
This collection is approximately 300 photographs of Regents Hill dormitories events including Homecoming, holidays, and mixers.
The Regents Hill complex was built in 1952 and houses approximately 400 women each year. It consists of two dormitories, Barnard and McGregor, and a dining hall, Stearns. Traditionally, the hall government is very active and works to establish vibrant hall spirit and togetherness within the community.
This collection consists of approximately 300 photographs of activities and events of Regents Hall, presumably taken by residents during the school years between 2000 and 2006. Many of the photographs are unlabeled and undated.
Approximately 175 physical photographs are placed at the beginning of the collection, followed by the two compact discs. In both sets of materials, they are filed in chronological order, and listed by the events depicted.
The two CDs have 130 images between them, which have been copied into WSU MASC’s digital archive. Images in both physical and digital format were noted and both copies were retained.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Kari Fass, Assistant Director of WSU’s Residence Life, donated this collection to the Washington State Libraries’ Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections on August 17, 2009, where they were retained as UPC 2009-02. The collection was processed in the summer of 2019 by Ellie Albrecht.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University -- Regents Hall -- Photographs.; Washington State University -- Buildings -- Photographs.
Dormitories -- Washington (State) -- Pullman.
Colleges and Universities; Washington (State); Photographs
- Mini Golf., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Homecoming., 2000 October (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Pumpkin Painting., 2000 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Thanksgiving., 2000 November (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Holiday Dinner., 2000 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Residents Learning to Knit., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Homecoming., 2001 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mix n’ Match Event., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Homecoming., 2005 October (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Holiday Decorating., 2005 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hall Government Retreat., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Valentine’s Day Skate., 2006 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Relay for Life., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Lucky Charm Dance., 2006 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- CD. Decorating; Government retreat; Valentine’s Day skate., 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CD. Lucky Charm dance; Government theme., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)